{
    "id": "21212c024e42401ba78ebc92910b00b6",
    "title": "Future Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………. you if you say that word again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will hit",
                "would hit"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "efef0227ed674229af12b11a6990be9e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... you tonight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will phone",
                "would phone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4425537c1ead426fa9c9af4fa449358f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I promise I …………………. you tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will visit",
                "would visit"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7e3dd4df838b4985bfeac3432ccbe413"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I’m starved.’ ‘I ……………… you something to eat.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will get",
                "would get",
                "am getting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c4b295192e41484196a3c0d64226390c"
        },
        {
            "question": "By next Christmas, we ..................... here for twenty years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "would be",
                "will have been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7e92cb9fcbe34c77b10de20beb899322"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ………………… the roof by Saturday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would finish",
                "will finish",
                "will have finished"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9d65b8e98a3047c3985c3d607248fdf1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ..................... by the time you reach her place.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will leave",
                "will have left",
                "would leave"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "83d92501b1a2435faf889efb5668c981"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t phone them now – they ………………… lunch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will have",
                "will be having",
                "would be"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "68b090e2c66548e69902dd46d6676bd7"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is no use phoning – they ………………….. by now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will leave",
                "will have left",
                "would leave"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8e14069e14dc4a689e8ce54a3551ef74"
        },
        {
            "question": "This time tomorrow, I ………………… with my grandchildren.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will play",
                "will be playing",
                "would be playing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "502e59229c114a6d8de6f14564e871e8"
        }
    ]
}